Guess it's time,
you better plug in all your nightlights.
What's out there through the attic floor?
Just some laughs, some fun, It's spooky galore!
Why don't you both follow my guidance?
To ensure this month never ends
la-la-la la la
Come with me, You will be
Ever thankful for my crimes, Against your kind
Find the hands of all the devils you have
brought drag you down
Bring all your friends
To witness genesis
Call till your throat bleeds
Lead them to me
Dance all the night away
Because it'll be your last
Give up your soul just for me
You're not a means to an end
No, you are my playthings
The screams, The gore, And all the chaos!
It's all like music to my ears
la-la-la la la
See my eyes, In the skies
Omnipresent, everywhere, You can not hide.
Children... Don't you want the spooky month to
last forever?